so
good afternoon everyone i'm adrika and
now it's finally time for our next
question question number four of the day
so let's just quickly start with our
question without any further due
so it's our fourth question of the day
and in total it will be our 59th
question so we are really getting close
to the target
so let's just so let's just quickly
start with our question
so while filling fuel
in your vehicle in your vehicle
your boss is calling you on your mobile
what will you do a quickly pick the call
until you will call back
b shout at the gas station employee
to fill the tank faster see
after leaving station park the car
in a secure location and then call back
or d pick the call instantly as you can
use the waiting time
so uh i'll just once again repeat the
question in hindi
[Music]
up
so you know answer this question as soon
as possible
and become a part of it and because
you know we can learn a lot by
[Music]
base is so you know we can learn a lot
by these simple steps of answering these
questions
and it is really simple also to answer
you know with the link in description
or from our facebook or from our youtube
page also you can answer it
the results will also be announced soon
of subscribe so i will just once again
repeat the question
while filling fuel in your vehicle
your boss is calling you on your mobile
what will you do a quickly pick the call
and tell you will call back b
shout at the gas station employees to
fill the tank fast
or see after leaving station
park the car in a park the car in a
secure location
and then call back or d
pick the call instantly as you can use
the
waiting
[Music]
so you know i hope that you all had
answered the previous questions as well
and you will be answering this question
as well as the other questions
which will be coming next also because
you know there are a lot of benefits
there are a lot of benefits which you
can get
with this simple step of answering these
questions
you know first of all you know that how
your behavior should be there on roads
and in certain situations regarding road
safety
and you know as you will get the uh
get to know that how your behavior
should be there
you will uh you will slowly start to
follow these traffic rules
and you know as each citizen starts to
follow these rules
our roads will uh will become safer
and as our roads will become safer
lesser accidents will happen
so you know you can become a part of us
you
can know that how your behavior should
be there on roads
and you can make the indian roads safer
as well as if you answer
if you answered the correct answer then
you can
also win some exciting prizes like a
bike safety kit for you and your family
or a car safety kit so just think about
give us is shortest step okay
uh each who does
[Applause]
[Music]
while driving and in certain situations
regarding road safety
and also uh and this can make
our roads safer safer and you can learn
that that you know
how your behavior should be there make
the road safer
and you can also win some exciting
prizes like a bike safety kit
or a car safety kit for you and your
family
so you know it's our benefits or
[Music]
you know every day we are having five
questions
every day we will be having five
questions in a gap of
two hours uh like abi three away three
o'clock okay
so after two hours our next question
question number five will be coming
the rest will be the rest five questions
will be coming tomorrow also
so you know like this every day we are
covering five questions
and they are in a gap of two hours and
each question is also valid for only
two hours and it's really simple to
answer you know
orissa marek
[Music]
so i will once again repeat this
question so
while filling fuel in your vehicle
your boss is calling you on your mobile
what will you do a quickly
quickly pick the call and tell
that you will call back or be
shout at the gas station employees
to fill the tank fast or see
after leaving station park the car
in a secure location and then call back
rd pick the call
[Music]
uh
our question question number four of the
day
so do answer this as soon as possible
tell your friends and family also about
it
is
safety is important so you know answer
this question become a part of us
and make the indian roads safer thank
you so much everyone
you